Here it comes.
The comet, it's coming
right for us!
No!
That was the comet, not me.
I'm gonna go find Pluto.
Now that it's no longer
a planet,
I bet it's all sad that
it's not relevant, like Kanye.
Come on, Freddie,
you got to try it.
You can actually go to space
without having to talk
to Elon Musk.
I'm too sad for space.
Space is all I'm gonna have
this next week.
He always gets like this
when I stay with my mom
for a little while.
Which I get. I'm the brightest
star in his universe.
Why's Gwen in town?
I thought she was in Zanzibar
for the next two months
marine biology-ing.
Underwater with her fellow
sea monsters.
Thanks for having
my back, Carly,
but it's been a year.
Gwen and I are in a good place.
I'm over the divorce.
Really? It would take me
a lot longer to get over
a gorgeous marine biologist
that travels the world
and has eyes that just...
see you.
And I'm less over it.
Gwen's in town because
Millicent's drama club is
doing Shakespeare scenes;
she's Juliet.
From what play?
Hark! Is there a little
thespian in here
who misses her mommy?
Me!
You said "thespian."
I love you so much,
but you smell
absolutely disgusting.
It's probably just
the stench of regret
over dumping Freddie.
Hello, Gwendolyn.
I see you're still trying
to make cargo pants happen.
Look who's talking, crop-top.
What you're smelling is
a mélange of
sea turtle afterbirth,
24 hours of middle-seat flights,
and three layovers
just to get to you.
Aka the stink of love.
Which I would have washed off,
but a pipe burst
in my apartment, so we need
to find a place to...
Stay with me.
Freddie, are you sure?
Yeah, you'd be there, too.
Of course. Millicent already
has her own room,
and we have an air mattress.
That I will apparently be
sleeping on.
Yeah, and you can
go take a shower.
I love this for us.
But really, go shower now.
I'll walk you out.
You've been here
long enough anyway.
It's so good to see you.
When can we stop pretending
to hate each other?
Never. I've been doing it
since the divorce.
Honestly, I kind of
love it, though.
It's like we're secret agents
that get blow-outs together.
Choo! Choo! Ha.
Harper, I didn't know
you liked pool.
I don't.
Disgusting little game.
I only learned so I could
ruin Spencer's life.
No!
What are you doing? I'm trying
to take a shot here!
I mean, what's the matter,
young child?
The person who was supposed
to design the costumes
for my Shakespeare performance
dropped out.
That's terrible.
Costumes are the most important
part of any show.
Of course you know that.
Clothes are your thing.
I mean, look at you right now.
Girl has taste.
If only you could
design the costumes.
Ooh.
Come on, Harper.
Volunteer is the right thing
to do.
I believe the children are
our future.
Calm down, Whitney.
I'll do it.
Pull those strings,
my little puppet master.
You know what's really horrible?
Our set designer also
dropped out.
What?! The set is the most
important part of any show.
Of course you know that.
Set design requires
a true artist.
Like you.
And look at this place.
Boy has taste.
I hear the trap,
but I'm too flattered
not to fall in it.
I'll do it.
Great. I'm gonna go upstairs
and call Mrs. Decker,
my drama teacher.
And by the way,
the volunteer who does
the most impressive work
always gets a prize.
Prize?
Wow, this place brings back
so many memories.
And so many rules.
Yep. No laughter
after 9:00 p.m.
Is it weird to say that I miss
her anti-tick shampoo?
Aw...
It's the locket with
Millicent's baby pics
before she grew
into her giant head.
"Gwen and Freddie"?
Why is she wearing this?
And why am I talking to myself?
Lots of questions.
This is
a disgusting little game.
Thank you.
Huge news! My costumes are about
to be even more incredible,
because the museum of velvet
is understandably
going out of business
and donating everything to me.
Huger news: my brain is
donating an amazing idea to me.
The set should be full marble
and sandstone. Booyah!
Should someone check
on Carly and Gwen
to make sure
they haven't killed each other?
What am I saying?
Gwen would destroy her.
You letting her stay
at your place?
Very evolved.
I didn't expect that from you.
We're co-parenting,
so we've learned to be good
around each other.
But seeing her again
does make me miss...
Aw, it's too embarrassing.
Ooh. Dish.
Actually, it is a dish.
She used to make
these unbelievable enchiladas.
It was her specialty.
Gwenchiladas.
- They're that good?
- Yes.
That is why I miss Gwen.
It's hard to admit,
but sometimes
I lie awake at night
imagining what it would be like
to have that again.
Honestly, just talking about it
makes me crave it even more.
I know it's bad
for my heart, but...
I still want it.
Sounds pretty cheesy.
Why don't you
just say how you feel
and ask her
to recreate the magic?
I've hinted at it, but she says
it's really complicated, and I
don't want to pressure her.
Hey. Where's my mom?
Wasting Freddie's water,
taking a shower.
I mean, the landlord pays
for the water, but still,
the Earth suffers.
Drop the act.
I know you're friends.
Hey.
When you guys chat,
does she ever mention
any divorced person she's
romantically interested in?
You mean Freddie?
Why do you ask?
Because I just
overheard him talking
about how much he misses my mom.
So weird, right?
Yeah. Very weird.
You know something.
Nuh.
My baby locket.
Don't open it.
Whoa.
Do you think they want
to get back together?
Aw, who cares?
I'm getting them back together
whether they want to or not.
We shouldn't interfere.
Unless we should.
No, we don't want
to manipulate them.
Unless we do.
- You make good points.
- Yep.
So, you're hooking up two people
who already gave it a shot
and got divorced?
You're like
the worst dating app ever.
Worse than the one you tried
for people
who look like celebrities?
Doppelbanger?
Michael B. Jordan.
More like Michael B. Ugly.
But making Ethiopian food
to recreate their first date?
Why are you working so hard
on this parent trap?
It's not a parent trap.
It's a parent suggestion.
Gwen's back at her apartment
dealing with the whole
burst pipe situation.
She thinks after that she's
gonna have a relaxing evening
with her daughter.
But I guess the joke's on her?
Exactly. 'Cause Millicent's
gonna come to our place
for a sleepover.
I just know how devastated
Freddie was When Gwen left.
If there's a chance
she wants him back,
the least I could do is put them
alone in a room together.
Alone? Aren't you forgetting
about someone?
No. I remembered.
Who's ready for a slumber party?
And look, I had a puzzle made
of Freddie doing a puzzle.
Nifty?
I told myself
I have to finish tonight,
or something horrible
would happen to him.
Okay, I'm sleeping at
Michael B. Ugly's house tonight.
Wow, Mrs. B.,
that was a really fun game
of Befriend, Marry, Scold.
Thank you.
You know, girls,
this may surprise you, but...
I have never been asked
to a sleepover.
What?!
Millicent, can you believe that?
I cannot.
It seems impossible that
that is possible.
Puzzle time!
I separated the pieces
into several piles:
freckles, dimples and skin tags.
I don't see any pieces
with facial stubble.
I know.
I had them photoshopped smooth.
Puzzle piece cut!
Not to worry...
I have miles of gauze.
Good thing I brought
my mini first aid kit.
This better be worth it.
I was gonna read a book tonight.
Magazine.
On your phone.
Probably the audio version.
It's still words.
Trust me, we got this.
My God. Do you have a date?
Is she here right now?
Yup. Apparently, she's you.
What?
"Dear parental units,
"wanted to give you
some alone time
"to reminisce
about the good old days.
"Enjoy dinner
in each other's company.
Love, your little miracle."
"Alone time"?
Why would she even...
Ethiopian food.
She's recreating our first date.
Not exactly. You don't have
that stupid soul patch.
And you got rid
of that terrible eyebrow ring.
Not by choice. I was on a dive,
and a barracuda bit it off.
Nah, yeah, it was super cute.
So, she's trying to set us up.
This is awkward.
Actually, it's perfect.
There's something
I've been meaning to tell you.
Okay, shoot.
I'll say this,
your dad has lovely pores.
Why are we doing this puzzle
when we could be spying
on my parents?
I know. It's killing me.
Dare we take a sneak peek?
We dare.
Good, you're already here.
I need to measure
the circumference of your head.
It's a very normal size.
That's not what
this tape measurer says. -Hey.
I'm making hats
for everyone in the play.
Or you can go ahead
and tell them to give me
the prize now, that's cool.
Thanks, okay.
- Come on.
- Aah!
- What...?
- Life-changing announcement!
That prize is mine.
The sandstone I was gonna use
is too heavy,
so I'm switching
to a lighter medium.
Toast.
It looks like stones,
but it's light and easy to move.
Ring, ring, ring! Hello?
Creativity Monthly? Why, yes,
I will be on your cover!
Click!
"Toast"? You can't build
a set out of toast.
Not the time to ask for details
from the weirdos.
Is what I would say
on opposite day.
Toast is great.
Go toast! Bye.
Hey, where are you two going?
It's time to "puzz" it up,
and I'm down a finger!
Spencer will help you.
He's the best at puzzles.
Isn't that right, Harper?
He's the best at nothing.
Yeah, I already got
one of Freddie's weird eyes.
I found his cowlick!
After Millicent's father
passed away,
I never thought I'd meet someone
who loved her as much as me.
"as much as I do."
I see why you divorced me.
Well... now it's time
for me to divorce somebody else.
Wait, that came out weird.
I'm seeing someone.
No!
I'm just kidding.
Honestly, I'm-I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
It's working.
We both knew this was
bound to happen.
We knew, too, we knew, too.
The only part I'm worried
about is Millicent..
Maybe this is
just too much for her.
I wish I had a way to know
how she's gonna react.
Well, should we go talk
to her right now?
No, I need to gauge her moods
over the next week.
Maybe even over the next year.
Aw, you're such a planner.
This is why
I fell in love with you.
Methinks I can speed
this process along.
I must away.
Hey, guys.
Harper, I thought
you'd be wearing a costume.
I know you love
a Ren fair wench moment.
Mrs. Decker said it would
"steal focus from the children."
Because my costumes are
too good.
Really? She didn't say anything
about my sets.
- Aw.
- 'Cause she was speechless!
Okay, I'm gonna go find
our little star.
- Who?
Millicent.
The entire reason
we're all here.
- Right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, that's why I'm here.
Program, Mrs. Benson?
Inside is a QR code
you can scan with your phone
to vote for which aspect
of the show you like the best...
The sets or the costumes!
But why wait till after the show
to fill it out?
Just turn down
your phone's brightness
and do it
during the boring parts.
My flip phone doesn't have
brightness or a camera.
Now hand me my program,
I like to plan my pee breaks.
Mr. Spencer, we have
a problem with the set.
- Apparently it's...
- falling apart.
I'm not surprised
your sets are crummy.
'Cause they're toast.
Are you playing a court jester?
'Cause this is serious!
Don't worry. I'll fix it.
I'm gonna need
some peanut butter, stat!
To stick the toast together?
I was just hungry,
but that's a great idea!
Move it!
There you are.
I can't believe you're gonna do
a grand romantic gesture
after your scene.
Do you want to run through
what you're gonna say?
Sure, I'll say something like,
"Thank you
for that thunderous applause.
A standing O?
That's unexpected."
Okay, rein it in, Meryl.
Get to the part
about your parents.
Right.
"This scene was dedicated
to two star-crossed lovers.
"My loving parents
Freddie and Gwen.
"You've managed to do what
Romeo and Juliet never could.
I'm so happy you two are getting
back together."
Wow.
That is really effective.
You know what,
bring it in, little sis.
Don't push it.
So I was thinking.
Sea turtles never worry about
telling their kids anything.
They just bury their eggs in
the sand and run away forever.
You think that could work
in this situation?
- Probably.
- Okay.
Hey, Freddie. Gwen.
What are you guys talking about?
We're trying to figure out how
to have a talk with Millicent.
Really?
What's the topic
of conversation?
Well, it's
kind of personal, but...
I already know what it is.
Are you proud of me?
I'm proud of me.
Wait, you know about Ernie?
Wait, what?
Who's Ernie?
He's Gwen's new boyfriend.
And don't worry about it,
Carly, I'm fine.
She told me
about him over dinner.
You have a boyfriend
and you didn't tell me?
But we're friends.
Whoa! Wait, hold up.
You guys are friends?
Since when?
Since always.
I just didn't want
to hurt your feelings.
Why would I be hurt?
Remember a few months ago
when I told you I was visiting
my dad in Italy?
- Yeah.
- Zanzibar.
Did she let you swim
with the turtles?
Ate right out of my hand.
Yeah, okay... this hurts.
Wait, if you're dating
some guy named Ernie,
then why was Freddie's picture
in your locket?
It's a present for Millicent
to help break the news.
I put pictures
of Freddie and me in it,
so she'd always have both of us
close to her heart.
My God, Millicent!
I-I got to go.
Excuse me. Sorry!
Excuse me.
Hear ye, hear ye and welcome.
Our first scene is
in fair Verona.
If your child has
a peanut allergy,
please avoid this area
or there will be much ado
about anaphylactic shock.
And now Romeo and Juliet.
O Romeo!
Romeo!
Wherefore art thou, Romeo?
Deny thy father
and refuse thy name.
What's in a name?
That which we call a rose
by any other name
would smell as sweet...
Psst!
Don't do it!
At the end!
Romeo, doff thy name,
and for that name
which is no part of thee,
take all myself.
No. This can't be good.
Shh!
My granddaughter is acting.
Hear ye, hear ye!
I cometh from the future.
That is
why forth I hath
this strange outfit.
Thou art not
the man I was expecting.
I bring news, my fairest Juliet.
You know that plan-eth
thou haveth
when thy scene is doneth?
Don't do it... eth.
Just tell me
what news thou hast for me,
annoying traveler!
Your mom and Freddie aren't
getting back together.
- Wha...?
- What?
Ooh!
Five-second rule.
Okay, we're going
to take a short intermission.
Close the curtains,
close the curtains.
I can't believe nobody voted
in our QR poll.
Yeah.
'Cause the QR code you made
is just a link
to the IHOP menu!
I want that prize!
I'm not supposed to say
anything, but Millicent told me
it's a companion falcon
for my main man Jericho.
What?! She told me it was
the Alexander McQueen
armadillo boots Lady Gaga wore
in her groundbreaking
music video "Bad Romance."
Just spitballing here,
but you don't think Millicent
just made up the prize,
knowing how competitive we get,
so that we'd drop everything
and do stuff
for her children's drama club,
do you?
- No.
- Nah.
-Actually, that totally
checks out. -Yeah.
Mr. Spencer,
Ms. Harper, the principal
would like to see you.
- No, we're in trouble.
- You're in trouble.
-I bet you I'm gonna get
those boots! -No, no, no.
I love it. Thank you.
You sure you're not upset that
we're not getting back together?
A little. I mean...
who wouldn't want
their family back together?
See, that's the thing...
We may not live together,
but we're still a family
and we're always gonna be.
I do like having
two Christmases and birthdays.
Wait.
If both of you marry
other people,
then get divorced again,
would that mean
that I get four Christmases
and birthdays?
Is there a reality show
that can speed this up?
Looks like all
of Millicent's scheming
that I had very little to do
with was worth it.
Carly, there you are.
I had so much fun
at our sleepover
that I don't think
I can sleep tonight,
not without another long hang.
Just us chicas.
I'll be by later
with my first aid kit
and some homemade dental floss.
See you then.
It's a participation ribbon.
Everybody gets one.
Including me.
That's it? That's the prize?
It's a public school.
There's no budget for prizes.
I'm shocked
there was even a play.
These ribbons weren't
the only prize, Fredd-o.
I'm not sure how it happened,
but Harper and I
have been appointed
co-chairs of the PTA.
Yeah!
The Parent Teacher Association?
- Yeah!
- Yep!
For parents and teachers.
Right?
Of which you are neither.
You got it!
Amazing!
The school was desperate.
No one else volunteered.
Ms. Carly? The principal would
like to see you next.
Of course, Olive.
Did I get
a cool blue ribbon, too?
No. You ruined the play.
You're in big trouble,
young lady.